[
    {
    "option1": "We have been go.",
    "option2": "We have been gone.",
    "option3": "We have been going.",
    "option4": "We had been going.",
    "question": "আমরা যেতে থাকছি",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "We shall be going.",
    "option2": "We shall  going.",
    "option3": "We shall be go.",
    "option4": "We shall go.",
    "question": "আমরা যেতে থাকবো",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "We had been gone.",
    "option2": "We would been going.",
    "option3": "We had been going.",
    "option4": "We had be going.",
    "question": "আমরা যেতে থাকলাম",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Are we been going ?",
    "option2": "Have we been go ?",
    "option3": "Have we be going ?",
    "option4": "Have we been going ?",
    "question": "আমরা কি যেতে থাকছি ?",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Will we be going ?",
    "option2": "Shall we be going ?",
    "option3": "Shall we be gone ?",
    "option4": "Shall we been going ?",
    "question": "আমরা কি যেতে থাকবো ?",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Had we been gone ?",
    "option2": "Had we been going ?",
    "option3": "Had we be going ?",
    "option4": "Did we been going ?",
    "question": "আমরা কি যেতে  থাকছিলাম ?",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "We had been gone.",
    "option2": "We had to go.",
    "option3": "We had going.",
    "option4": "We had gone.",
    "question": "আমরা গেলাম",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Had we going ?",
    "option2": "Had we been gone ?",
    "option3": "Had we gone ?",
    "option4": "Had we went ?",
    "question": "আমরা কি গেলাম ?",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "We could have gone.",
    "option2": "We could have going.",
    "option3": "We could had gone.",
    "option4": "We could have went.",
    "question": "আমরা যেতে পারতাম",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Could we had gone ?",
    "option2": "Could we have gone ?",
    "option3": "Could we have going ?",
    "option4": "Did we have gone ?",
    "question": "আমরা কি যেতে পারতাম ?",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "We would be gone.",
    "option2": "We would had gone.",
    "option3": "We would have going.",
    "option4": "We would have gone.",
    "question": "আমরা যেতে পারতাম",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Would we has gone ?",
    "option2": "Would we have gone ?",
    "option3": "Would we have go ?",
    "option4": "Would we have to gone ?",
    "question": "আমরা কি যেতে পারতাম ?",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "We should have gone.",
    "option2": "We should have going.",
    "option3": "We should had gone.",
    "option4": "We should have to go.",
    "question": "আমাদের যেতে পারা উচিৎ ছিল",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Shall we have gone ?",
    "option2": "Should we have go ?",
    "option3": "Should we have gone ?",
    "option4": "Should we have going ?",
    "question": "আমাদের কি যেতে পারা উচিৎ ছিল ?",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "We may be gone.",
    "option2": "We may have gone.",
    "option3": "We may be going.",
    "option4": "We may had gone.",
    "question": "আমরা যেতে পারতাম",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Shall we have gone ?",
    "option2": "May we have going ?",
    "option3": "May we be gone ?",
    "option4": "May we have gone ?",
    "question": "আমরা কি যেতে পারতাম ?",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "We cannot but going.",
    "option2": "We cannot but go.",
    "option3": "We cannot be go.",
    "option4": "We cannot had go.",
    "question": "আমরা না গিয়ে পারি না",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "We cannot help going.",
    "option2": "We cannot help go.",
    "option3": "We cannot be going.",
    "option4": "We cannot help gone.",
    "question": "আমরা না গিয়ে পারি না",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    }
]